you know you know it's illegal to take the video of someone under 18 without the parents
permission you need to blur their face when you take the video of them no it's in the public
street they're pretty cool glasses that's all i'm gonna say thank you i'm telling you
you're not from kids even in public no in the street it's fine oh you're recording too
this is this is not in the torah what is this what does it mean
who is messiah the rabbi yeah the rabbi this is this is an abomination to the process
that chicken is in that position because of the poros because of the demand that you're creating
so you think in the farms they don't die why not they shouldn't be in the farms
animals are living autonomous beings creations of god
they use the wild chickens fly but they feed them a lot to the fatter and they can't pick them up
yes right he said yes yes yes he says the kingdom of heaven on earth live all animals are free
the wolf shall lay with the land the lion that eats straw like the ox you don't even know what he's
saying it's a different language huh what are you talking about yes yes yes yes isaiah isaiah the
prophet you don't know your own prophets yes yes yes yes yes yes yes no killing no murder good good good
who speaks english
how are you meant to eat them you want to eat them alive you want to eat them alive you're not
no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
How do you say "tip stock"? Murder?
Kill chicken.
Is it abomination to the process?
Yes.
What's your name?
No, why is it still a name?
You support Israel or Palestine?
Huh?
I don't support nations in this period.
Israel is a name that means "me who wrestling with God".
Most of you don't support nations in this period, right?
I support the idea.
Netanyahu.
And Benvi.
Say what?
Absolutely.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Dead shipments hanging out of Israel.
Whoa, whoa.
And dead in Gaza?
Huh?
Dead in Gaza?
And Gaza dead also, you support?
I don't support death of any human or any of you.
October 7th.
Yeah.
Murder, not good.
No?
Murder Palestinians and Jews are bad.
No.
What before?
What do you mean before?
From the beginning of time, murder is bad.
Human animal.
Where are you born?
Huh?
In America.
What city?
It doesn't matter.
Why?
It's irrelevant.
Where are you going to enter?
Where are you born?
Ah, Israel.
Tel Aviv.
Cool.
I've been many times.
You want the name of the hospital also?
Yeah, I've been many times.
I've been to Israel too.
Yeah, Israel too.
Huh?
I've been to Israel too.
I've been to Israel.
Good camp, you know?
Good?
Oh, yeah.
Holy land.
But you know what is it?
You know what is it?
You know what?
You're Christian?
I'm a Nazarene.
What does it mean?
Nazarene?
Nazarene.
What does it mean?
Huh?
What is Nazarene?
Oh, no.
You're Christian?
Nazarene.
Oh, what's it?
I follow Yeshua.
Yeshua.
Yeshua will be a Jewish.
Huh?
Yeah.
Galilean.
Nazarene.
Oh, thank you.
How you doing?
Good.
You're with Reina, right?
I am with Reina.
She's over there?
She's over there somewhere.
And there's a dead chicken hanging out of the truck here.
Totally.
I got you.
I can't do anything about it right now.
I got to get you guys squared away.
What's the name of the church?
Share some of it.
Everywhere.
Yeah, I can help you, right?
Yeah?
Okay.
You have freedom.
Freedom of religion.
But not freedom to take life.
Freedom to kill?
This?
I'm against all life.
I'm against all, all killing of life.
Ah, you big motherfucker.
My god says do not kill.
That's in the Torah.
Do not kill.
You have Wikipedia?
Wikipedia?
Do not kill.
So...
What is this?
Is this a movie?
It's a movie.
Murders.
Of humans.
Watch it.
And animals.
Very not interesting.
Huh?
Because...
Very not interesting.
It quotes the prophets all throughout.
The prophets are interesting to you?
You don't have a lot of voice.
Two thousand.
Not a lot.
You don't have a lot of voice.
Two thousand.
Not a lot.
Huh?
You don't have a lot of voice.
I'm not...
That's...
That's Tiktok.
I don't do Tiktok.
No.
This is YouTube.
That's my personal YouTube channel.
No.
This is what you say.
You have two thousand voice.
Two thousand views.
Yeah.
You're not famous.
I think you will...
So you read the Torah.
Yeah.
You know Genesis.
Genesis 1.
God gave us fruit and herbs.
Vegetables.
To eat.
Yeah.
Okay.
I know about Genesis 9.
After that, God said to eat animals.
Salem.
Well, I'm just reminding you guys of our design.
Our human design is vegan.
Vegan.
Really says...
No.
I'm saying that our design is vegan.
I got you.
Our design is human.
Is vegan.